<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HarvestX | Top on HarvestX</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/</link><description>Recent content in HarvestX | Top on HarvestX</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>©HarvestX Inc. 2024</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:07:39 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://harvestx.jp/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HarvestX Opens New Branch Office in Hamamatsu City</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20231101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:07:39 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20231101/</guid><description>HarvestX Inc. has established the Hamamatsu Office in the Co-startup Space &amp;amp; Community FUSE in Hamamatsu City, Shizuoka Prefecture. The opening of the new office will strengthen its business expansion of ‘HarvestX’, an automated strawberry cultivation system.
Hamamatsu City, the hometown of founder Ichikawa, is one of the leading strawberry growing areas in Japan. Shizuoka Prefecture, including Hamamatsu City, is one of the top producers in terms of production volume and acreage, and there are many large-scale production factories in the area.</description></item><item><title>HarvestX won the Runner-up Grand Prix at the ICC Summit KYOTO 2023 Design &amp; Innovation Award.</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20230919/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 20:52:55 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20230919/</guid><description>HarvestX, Inc. was awarded the Runner-up Grand Prix in the main program Design &amp;amp; Innovation Award at the Industry Co-Creation (ICC) Summit KYOTO 2023, held in Kyoto from September 4 to 7, 2023.
ICC Summit is a business conference based on the concept of &amp;ldquo;Learning together, creating industries together&amp;rdquo;. More than 400 top leaders (managers, executives, and professionals) active on the front lines take the stage to exchange high-quality opinions on industry trends and management over the course of three days.</description></item><item><title>HarvestX, an automated strawberry cultivation solution to be provided sequentially from summer 2023.</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20221221/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20221221/</guid><description>HarvestX, Inc. has developed a new robot, XV3, and will begin offering the HarvestX, automated strawberry cultivation solution in the summer of 2023.
HarvestX is a solution that automates plant management, pollination, and harvesting in the strawberry production process at indoor vertical farms to achieve stable production. HarvestX, Inc. has been developing prototypes of automated pollination and harvesting robots (XV1 and XV2), and has now developed a new robot, XV3, with higher work efficiency than the previous demonstration models.</description></item><item><title>Senior Vice Minister visited HarvestX Lab.</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20220419/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20220419/</guid><description>Hideyuki Tanaka, Senior Vice Minister of Education, Culture, Sports, Science and Technology, visited HarvestX Lab, our research and development facility for a fully automated strawberry cultivation robot system, in the University of Tokyo Entrepreneur Lab. After tasting strawberries grown in the lab, he had discussions with CEO Ichikawa and Tokyo University officials.</description></item><item><title>HarvestX has secured a total of 150 million yen in funding!</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20220330_1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20220330_1/</guid><description>HarvestX Inc. (Head office: Bunkyo-Ku, Tokyo; President: Yuki Ichikawa) has raised a total of 150 million yen in funding from “ANRI No.4 Investment Limited Partnership” (Representative: Anri Samata) managed by venture capital ANRI, the Open Innovation Promotion No. 1 Investment Limited Partnership managed by the University of Tokyo Innovation Platform Co., Ltd. (Headquarters: Hongo, Bunkyo-Ku, Tokyo; President: Katsuhiko Oizumi) and “DEEPCORE TOKYO No.2 Investment Limited Partnership” managed by DEEPCORE Inc..</description></item><item><title>HarvestX partnered with National Institute of Technology, Tokuyama College.</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20220330_2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 09:59:50 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20220330_2/</guid><description>HarvestX Inc. (Head office: Bunkyo-Ku, Tokyo; President: Yuki Ichikawa) partnered with National Institute of Technology, Tokuyama College and established its second office within the college to start joint research.This is the first time in Japan that a start-up company has established an office in a national institute of technology.
(CEO and CTO of HarvestX and members of Tokuyama College AT Team at Tokuyama College)
Through this collaboration, we can accelerate development of more efficient pollinating attachment toward fully automated agriculture.</description></item><item><title>HarvestX Joins Microsoft for Startups</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20211216/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20211216/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that HarvestX has been accepted to the Microsoft for Startups program, which is designed to strengthen the development of promising startups.
Microsoft for Startups helps B2B startups successfully scale their companies by providing them with access to innovative technology, hands-on mentorship, and access to new sales opportunities. The resources and supports provided by Microsoft will allow us to continue to improve our automatic pollinating and harvesting robot.</description></item><item><title>XV2, Our New Automatic Pollinating and Harvesting Robot</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20211115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20211115/</guid><description>HarvestX Inc. (Head office: Bunkyo-Ku, Tokyo; President: Yuki Ichikawa) released XV2, a new automatic pollinating and harvesting robot prototype with higher mobility and efficiency than the previous prototype.
New Features of XV2 Suitable for multi-layer vertical farming system Autonomous driving by magnetic guidance system Equipped with a function to change harvesting trays to increase loading capacity of harvested strawberries With this new robot specialized for indoor vertical farms, we will continue to develop products with even greater adaptability to the actual cultivation environment.</description></item><item><title>HarvestX Joins NVIDIA Inception Program</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20211018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20211018/</guid><description>HarvestX has joined the NVIDIA Inception Program, which is designed to nurture startups revolutionising industries with advancements in AI and data sciences. The NVIDIA Inception Program will benefit HarvestX by offering NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s technology and marketing support.
NVIDIA Inception is a virtual accelerator program that helps startups during critical stages of product development, prototyping and deployment. Every Inception member gets a custom set of ongoing benefits, from hardware grants and marketing support to training with deep learning experts.</description></item><item><title>We have received a grant from the Mitsubishi UFJ Technology Development Foundation</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20210922/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20210922/</guid><description>We are proud to announce that our robot system development project &amp;ldquo;Development of Attachments with Dataset Creation Method, Machine Learning and Tool Exchange Mechanism for Pollinating and Harvesting Robots&amp;rdquo; has received &amp;ldquo;2021 Research and Development Grants&amp;rdquo; from the Mitsubishi UFJ Technology Development Foundation. The objective of this grant is to support venture companies in their research and development of new technologies and products.
About Mitsubishi UFJ Technology Development Foundation (Japanese)</description></item><item><title>We established HarvestX Lab, a research and development facility for robotic systems</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20210621/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20210621/</guid><description>HarvestX Inc. (Head office: Bunkyo-Ku, Tokyo; President: Yuki Ichikawa) established HarvestX Lab, a research and development facility for fully automated strawberry cultivation robot system, in the University of Tokyo Entrepreneur Lab.
HarvestX Lab is a dedicated R&amp;amp;D facility where we can conduct tests throughout the year in order to add more items for verification and evaluation of the robot system and to accelerate the testing cycle.
By using the same cultivation facilities as those of indoor farming companies, we will reduce the difference between the development environment and the operation environment, and aim to improve the functions and quality of our products.</description></item><item><title>We have raised a total of 50 million yen in funding.</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20210118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 09:59:50 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20210118/</guid><description>HarvestX Inc. (Head office: Bunkyo-Ku, Tokyo; President: Yuki Ichikawa) has raised a total of 50 million yen in funding from independent venture capital &amp;ldquo;ANRI No.4 Investment Limited Partnership&amp;rdquo; (Representative: Anri Samata), the Open Innovation Promotion No. 1 Investment Limited Partnership managed by the University of Tokyo Innovation Platform Co., Ltd. (Headquarters: Hongo, Bunkyo-Ku, Tokyo; President: Katsuhiko Oizumi), Soichiro Kawai, Keisuke Sogawa, and Kunihiro Tanaka.
Press release(Japanese)</description></item><item><title>HarvestX has been selected to UTokyo IPC 1st Round</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20201020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20201020/</guid><description>HarvestX has been selected to the &amp;lsquo;1st Round&amp;rsquo;, an incubation program run by UTokyo IPC(Innovation Platform for the University of Tokyo).
Press release UTokyo IPC: https://www.utokyo-ipc.co.jp/2020/10/utokyoipc-1stround_3rd_final/ (Japanese)</description></item><item><title>Mitsui Chemicals Award at the Agritech Grand Prix 2020</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20200930/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20200930/</guid><description>HarvestX was honored to be a recipient of Mitsui Chemicals Award at the Agritech Grand Prix 2020.
About Agritech Grand Prix 2020 (Japanese)</description></item><item><title>We won the Todai To Texas Demo Day Award!</title><link>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20190930/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://harvestx.jp/en/news/20190930/</guid><description>We are proud to announce that HarvestX is awarded the Demo Day Award at Todai to Texas 2020. As a recipient, we will have an exhibition booth at SXSW 2020 to be held in Austin, Texas, USA in March 2020. SXSW(South by Southwest) is held every March in Austin, celebrating the convergence of tech, film, and music industries.
&amp;lsquo;Todai To Texas&amp;rsquo; is a contest organized by the Division of University Corporate Relations, University of Tokyo.</description></item></channel></rss>